<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio on </title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/portfiolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolio on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>email@example.com (Iiro Purola)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>email@example.com (Iiro Purola)</webMaster>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/portfiolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Personal Curriculum Vitae and Portfolio Website with Hugo and Tailwind CSS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/portfiolio/personal-curriculum-vitae-and-portfolio-website-with-hugo-and-tailwind-css/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>email@example.com (Iiro Purola)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/portfiolio/personal-curriculum-vitae-and-portfolio-website-with-hugo-and-tailwind-css/</guid>
      <description>Overview: The project was an undertaking to design and create a personal Curriculum Vitae and portfolio website utilizing the Hugo static site generator and Tailwind CSS. This initiative aimed to master Hugo and Tailwind CSS, with a special emphasis on learning AI Prompt Engineering, which was heavily used during the site&amp;rsquo;s development.&#xA;Challenge: The objective was to gain expertise in Hugo, Tailwind CSS, and AI Prompt Engineering while creating a professional, well-structured, and visually appealing portfolio website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tailored AVD Desktops and Jump Environments for Specific User Groups</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/portfiolio/tailored-avd-desktops-and-jump-environments-for-specific-user-groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>email@example.com (Iiro Purola)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/portfiolio/tailored-avd-desktops-and-jump-environments-for-specific-user-groups/</guid>
      <description>Overview: The client requested a design and implementation of Azure Virtual Desktop (AVD) environments that cater to three distinct user groups in their organization. The project involved the creation of three separate workloads: a custom customer service desktop, and two versions of the Jump environment, each serving unique user requirements and access privileges.&#xA;Challenge: The project presented a multifaceted challenge. The client required a custom customer service desktop equipped with specific software, and two versions of Jump environments – one displaying selected portals via a browser, and another solely designed for Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) associations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transition to Serverless IT Infrastructure with Azure AD and Intune</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/portfiolio/transition-to-serverless-it-infrastructure-with-azure-ad-and-intune/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>email@example.com (Iiro Purola)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/portfiolio/transition-to-serverless-it-infrastructure-with-azure-ad-and-intune/</guid>
      <description>Overview: This project revolved around modernizing a company&amp;rsquo;s IT infrastructure by migrating it to a serverless model. The endeavor involved replacing the traditional on-premises Active Directory with Azure Active Directory and introducing Microsoft Intune for robust device management. The project also encompassed a shift from the conventional print server to Printix, along with strengthening the security and backup system of the Microsoft cloud environment and emails.&#xA;Challenge: The company previously lacked a comprehensive device management system and had an outdated on-premises Active Directory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Website Development for a Transport Company</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/portfiolio/website-development-for-a-transport-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>email@example.com (Iiro Purola)</author>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/portfiolio/website-development-for-a-transport-company/</guid>
      <description>Overview: The project involved the creation of two distinct websites for a transport company. The first website, aimed at customers, would provide information about the company&amp;rsquo;s services, while the second, an intranet site, would serve as a secure platform for entrepreneurs in the transport industry to access exclusive content. The project was independently planned and implemented using WordPress and hosted on a Finnish service provider.&#xA;Challenge: The client needed both websites to be fast, user-friendly, visually appealing, and easily editable.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
